

Nataliia Prokopenko

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

CONTACT



+48 698 906 659



natalijaprokopenko@yahoo.com



natalijaprokopenko.netlify.app

ABOUT ME

Hard-working, creative and proactive.

COMPETENCES

Attentive to details Front-End Developer with the main area of expertise in Front-End Development: React, JavaScript, Responsive Web Development, API integration, Git. Who possesses theoretical and practical knowledge in software development. Who was involved in different types of SDLC methodologies: Agile, SCRUM. Who has skills to analyze requirements for development. Has strong problem solving skills. Has high level of negotiation skills.

SKILLS

React JavaScript **API** integration Responsive Web Design HTML, CSS, Bootstrap

TOOLS

VSCode Node js Git Figma

LANGUAGES

Ukrainian - Native English - Upper intermediate Polish - Intermediate

WORK EXPERIENCE

SheCodes | 2022-2023

Responsive Web Design, JavaScript, React, API integration. Study and practice programming.

FreeCodeCamp | 2019 - 2021

Responsive Web Design. Java script Algorithms and Data Structures.

SoloLearn | 04.2019 - 09.2019

Certifications: "HTML, CSS Fundamentals courses", "JavaScript, ¡Query Tutorial courses".

Alfa-Bank | 11.2007 - 09.2011, Kyiv, Ukraine

Quality Assurance Engineer/Risk Manager

Collaboration with a Product Owner, a Business Analyst to clarify requirements. Preparing test plans, test scenario, test cases. Test execution. Test results. Exit criteria. Functional testing. UAT. Project: Implementation of NBSM software. alfabank.ua

Delta Bank | 06.2006 - 11.2007, Kyiv, Ukraine

Tester/Product owner

Collaboration with end users. UAT. Test cases creating. Functional testing. Bug reports. Test execution. Exit criteria. Project: decision making system.

EDUCATION

Interregional Academy of Personnel, Kyiv, Ukraine

Finance 2005/2009

IT Step, Lviv, Ukraine

Programming 2017/2018